AFSCME, District Council 37 Photographs PHOTOS.247
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Public Employee Press Files, [1959]-[2001].
  - Vol. 38 No. 5 Issue Date: Apr 18, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 38 No. 6 Issue Date: May 9, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 38 No. 7 Issue Date: May 30, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 38 No. 8 Issue Date: Jun 20, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 38 No. 9 Issue Date: Jul 11, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 38 No. 10 Issue Date: Aug 22, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 38 No. 11 Issue Date: Sep 12, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 38 No. 12 Issue Date: Oct 3, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 38 No. 13 Issue Date: Oct 24, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Vol. 38 No. 14 Issue Date: Nov 14, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Vol. 38 No. 15 Issue Date: Dec 5, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Vol. 38 No. 16 Issue Date: Dec 26, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 39 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 23, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 39 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 13, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 39 No. 3 Issue Date: Mar 6, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 39 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 27, 1998 (I) (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 39 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 27, 1998 (II) (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 39 No. 5 Issue Date: Apr 17, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 39 No. 6 Issue Date: May 8, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 39 No. 7 Issue Date: May 29, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 39 No. 8 Issue Date: Jun 19, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 39 No. 9 Issue Date: Jul 10, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 39 No. 10 Issue Date: Aug 21, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 39 No. 11 Issue Date: Sep 11, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 39 No. 12 Issue Date: Oct 2, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 39 No. 13 Issue Date: Oct 23, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 39 No. 14 Issue Date: Nov 13, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 39 No. 15 Issue Date: Dec 4, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 39 No. 16 Issue Date: Dec 25, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 40 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 12, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 40 No. 3 Issue Date: Mar 5, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 40 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 26, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 40 No. 5 Issue Date: Apr 16, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 40 No. 6 Issue Date: May 7, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 40 No. 7 Issue Date: Jun 4, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 40 No. 8 Issue Date: Jun 25, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 40 No. 9 Issue Date: Jul 16, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 40 No. 10 Issue Date: Aug 27, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 40 No. 11 Issue Date: Sep 17, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 40 No. 12 Issue Date: Oct 8, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 40 No. 13 Issue Date: Nov 5, 1999 (I) (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 40 No. 13 Issue Date: Nov 5, 1999 (II) (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 40 No. 14 Issue Date: Nov 26, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 40 No. 15 Issue Date: Dec 17, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 41 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 28, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 41 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 25, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 41 No. 3 Issue Date: Mar 17, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 41 No. 3 Issue Date: Mar 17, 2000 Black History Month (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 41 No. 4 Issue Date: Apr 7, 2000 (I) (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 41 No. 4 Issue Date: Apr 7, 2000 (II) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 41 No. 5 Issue Date: May 5, 2000 (I) (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 41 No. 5 Issue Date: May 5, 2000 (II) (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 41 No. 6 Issue Date: May 26, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 41 No. 7 Issue Date: Jun 16, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 41 No. 8 Issue Date: Jul 7, 2000 (I) (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 41 No. 8 Issue Date: Jul 7, 2000 (II) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 41 No. 9 Issue Date: Aug 31, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 41 No. 10 Issue Date: Sep 22, 2000 (I) (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 41 No. 10 Issue Date: Sep 22, 2000 (II) (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 41 No. 10 Issue Date: Sep 22, 2000 (III) (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 41 No. 10 Issue Date: Sep 22, 2000 (IV) (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 41 No. 10 Issue Date: Sep 22, 2000 (V) (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 41 No. 10 Issue Date: Sep 22, 2000 (VI) (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 41 No. 11 Issue Date: Oct 27, 2000 (I) (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 41 No. 11 Issue Date: Oct 27, 2000 (II) (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 41 No. 11 Issue Date: Oct 27, 2000 (III) (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 41 No. 12 Issue Date: Nov 24, 2000 (I) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 41 No. 12 Issue Date: Nov 24, 2000 (II) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 41 No. 12 Issue Date: Nov 24, 2000 (III) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 41 No. 12 Issue Date: Nov 24, 2000 (IV) (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 41 No. 12 Issue Date: Nov 24, 2000 (V) (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 41 No. 12 Issue Date: Nov 24, 2000 (VI) (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 41 No. 12 Issue Date: Nov 24, 2000 (VII) (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 41 No. 12 Issue Date: Nov 24, 2000 (VIII) (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 41 No. 13 Issue Date: Dec 15, 2000 (I) (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 41 No. 13 Issue Date: Dec 15, 2000 (II) (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 41 No. 13 Issue Date: Dec 15, 2000 (III) (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 42 No. 1 Issue Date: Feb 2001 (I) (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 42 No. 1 Issue Date: Feb 2001 (II) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 42 No. 2 Issue Date: Mar 2001 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 42 No. 3 Issue Date: Apr 2001 (I) (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 42 No. 3 Issue Date: Apr 2001 (II) (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 42 No. 3 Issue Date: Apr 2001 (III) (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 42 No. 3 Issue Date: Apr 2001 (IV) Black History Month (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 42 No. 4 Issue Date: Apr 2001 Special Edition (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 42 No. 5 Issue Date: May 2001 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - PEP Oversize, [1968-1998] (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Series II: Locals Files, 1948-2002.
  - Local 149: Department of Parks [Defunct], 1964-1965, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Local 154: New York City Amalgamated Professional Employees [and Defunct- Multiple Titles, see Appendix 2], 1963-1964, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Local 154: New York City Amalgamated Professional Employees Newsletter, 1986-2001, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Local 299: AFSCME (Recreation Employees), 1963-1982 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Local 299, Undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Local 299: Summer Playcamps, 1968-1984, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Local 299: "Summer Playcamps Are Summer Fun" Book, 1979, 1984, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Local 299: Recreation Brochure, 1976, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Local 371: Social Services Employees Union, 1964-1992 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Local 371, Undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Local 371, Undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Local 372: New York City Board of Education Employees, 1963-[1984] (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Local 372, 1991-1998, undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Local 372, Undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Local 372, Undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Local 372, Undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Local 374: Quasi-Public Employees (bulk from "Botany and Books" Newsletter), 1976-1988, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Local 375: Civil Service Technical Guild, [1957]-1988, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Local 375 Newsletter, 1982-1990 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Local 375 Newsletter, 1990-2000 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Local 375 Newsletter, Undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Local 376: New York City Construction Laborers, Highway Repairers & Watershed Maintainers (includes Newsletter), 1965-1998, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Local 384: City University of New York (CUNY) and Educational Opportunity Centers (includes "Locally Speaking" Newsletter), 1965-2000, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Local 420: Municipal Hospital Employees Union--Demonstrations and Rallies, [1956]-1999 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Local 420: Demonstrations and Rallies, Undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Local 420: Events and Members, 1948-1999 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Local 420: Events and Members, Undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Local 420: Events and Members, Undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Local 420: Events and Members, Undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Local 420: Events and Members, Undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Local 420: Publications, [1973-1995], undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (Shot for or published in PEP), [1967-1968] (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Local 436: United Federation of Nurses and Epidemiologists, 1975, 1982, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Local 436 Newsletter, [1988, 1999] (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Local 461: New York City Lifeguards, Undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Local 508: New York City Lifeguard Supervisors, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Local 768: Health Services Employees, 1963-1980, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Local 768 Newsletter, 1984-1996 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Local 768 Newsletter, 1997-2002 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Local 768 Newsletter, Undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Local 924: New York City Laborers, 1956-[1977] (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Local 924, Undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Local 957: New York City Housing Authority Clerical Employees, 1963-1995, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Local 957: "Figures and Keys" Newsletter, 1978-1999, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Local 983: New York City Motor Vehicle Operators, 1957-1986 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Local 983, Undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Local 983 Newsletter, [1999]-2001, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Local 1062: Supervisors of Automotive Plants & Equipment Employees, 1965-[1979], undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Local 1070: Court, County & Department of Probation Employees (includes "Newsline" Newsletter), 1955-1996, undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Local 1087: New York City Prevailing Rate Employees, 1965-[1976], undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Local 1113: New York City Finance Administrative Employees and City Investigators, 1957-[1995], undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Local 1113 [Newsletter?], [1974-1991], undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Local 1157: New York City Department of Transportation Supervisory Employees, 1967, undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Local 1189: New York City Psychologists, 1963-1988 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Local 1219: New York City Real Estate Employees, 1963-[1993], undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Local 1251: New York City Board of Education Clerical-Administrative Employees "Digest" Newsletter, [1986] (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Local 1306: American Museum of Natural History, 1963-1998, undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Local 1308: Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (TBTA) Sergeants and Lieutenants [Defunct], [1964], undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Local 1320: New York City Sewage Treatment & Senior Sewage Treatment Workers, Undated (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Local 1320: "Open Line" Newsletter, 1966, [1983-2000], undated (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Local 1321: Queens Library Guild (includes Newsletter), [1976-1995], undated (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Local 1322: New York City Department of Environmental Protection (DEP) Supervisory Employees, 1963, undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Local 1331: Air Pollution Control [Defunct], 1963-1964, undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Local 1359: Rent Regulation Services Employees (includes Newsletter), 1963-1966, undated (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Local 1396: Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (TBTA) [Defunct], [1965]-1978, undated (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Local 1407: New York City Accountants, Statisticians & Actuaries, 1964-[1989], undated (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Local 1414: Water Shed Employees [Defunct], 1963, undated (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Local 1455: New York City Traffic Employees, [1966-1973], undated (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Local 1457: New York City Juvenile Center Employees (includes Newsletter), 1963-[1985], undated (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Local 1467: [Defunct- Name Unknown], 1962-1964, undated (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Local 1482: Brooklyn Library Guild (includes Newsletter), 1966-[1982], undated (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Local 1485: Anti-Poverty Employees [Defunct], [1966-1967], undated (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Local 1501: New York City Zoological Employees, [1961-1964] (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Local 1503: Metropolitan Museum of Art (includes "ART-A-FACTS" Newsletter), 1966-[1994], undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Local 1504: American Museum of Natural History (AMNH) Supervisors [Defunct], Undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Local 1505: New York City Attendants, Park Service Workers, City Park Workers & Debris Removers (includes "Our Voice Unity" Newsletter), 1963-[1999], undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Local 1506: New York City Department of Parks Climbers & Pruners, 1964, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Local 1507: New York City Department of Parks Gardeners, [1964-1974], undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Local 1508: Uniformed Park Supervisors, 1963-[1984], undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Local 1509: Youth Services Agency [Defunct], 1965, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Local 1549: New York City Clerical-Administrative Employees--Clerical Dispatch Chapter Newsletter, [1986], undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Local 1549: Comptroller's Chapter Newsletter, [1989], undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Local 1549: Consumer Affairs Chapter Newsletter, [1985] (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Local 1549: Department of Social Services Chapter Newsletter ("Insite"), [1986-2000], undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Local 1549: Hospitals Chapter Newsletter, [1986-1999], undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Local 1549: Police Communications Technician Chapter Newsletter, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Local 1549: Albert Diop Portrait, Undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Local 1549: Black History Month Celebration, Undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Local 1549: Puerto Rican Day Parade, [1990] (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Local 1549: Education Conference, [1994] (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Local 1549: AFSCME Conventions (Miami & Hawaii), 1990, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Local 1549: AFSCME Convention, 1549 Women's Committee, Jun 1990 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Local 1549: Rallies, Undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Local 1549: Unidentified Events, [1993], undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Local 1549: Unidentified Events, Undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Local 1549: Unidentified Events, Undated (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Local 1559: American Museum of Natural History, 1963, undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Local 1597: New York City Custodial Assistant Employees, 1963-1974, undated (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Local 1655: Metropolitan Transportation Authority Clerical-Administrative Employees, 1962-1989, undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Local 1655 Newsletter, [1983-1996], undated (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Local 1707: Community and Social Agency Employees [Defunct], 1962-1964, undated (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Local 1757: New York City Assessors, Appraisers & Housing Development Specialists (includes "Shield & Blade" Newsletter), 1963, [1992-1994], undated (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Local 1759: Consumer Affairs Inspectors, 1963- [1966], undated (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Local 1783: New York City Housing Authority Maintenance and Operation Employees [Defunct], 1963-1964, undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Local 1784: Hospitals and Professional and Clerical Administrative [Defunct], 1963-1966, undated (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Local 1795: Stationary Firemen [Defunct], [1966]-1974, undated (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Local 1797: New York City Custodial Supervisors, [1979] (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Local 1930: New York Public Library Guild (bulk "Newsline" Newsletter), 1968-2000, undated (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Local 1931: Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (TBTA) Maintenance Employees (includes newsletter), [1976-1993], undated (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Local 2021: New York City Off-Track Betting (OTB) Corporation Employees, 1971-1984, undated (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Local 2021: OTB Strike, [Apr 1979] (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Local 2021: Newsletter, 1982-1996, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Local 2021: Brochure, 1974-[1992], undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Local 2021: Unidentified Publication, [1974-1984], undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Local 2054: New York City College Assistants, [1976], undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Local 2507: Uniformed Emergency Medical Technicians (EMTs) & Paramedics of the Fire Department of New York (FDNY), [1977-1985], undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Local 2507: "Lifeline to New York" Newsletter, [1981-1986], undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Local 2627: New York City Electronic Data Processing Personnel, 1988-[1992], undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Local 2906: New York City Marine Workers, Undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Local 3621: Uniformed Emergency Medical Service (EMS) Officers Union, Fire Department of New York (FDNY) Newsletter, [1993, 1996], undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Various Locals: Unidentified, Undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Series III: DC 37 History, [1946]-[1994].
  - Subseries A: Events, [1946]-1993.
    - AFSCME Agreement with New York City Mayor O'Dwyer, [Aug 1946] (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Division of Placement & Unemployment Insurance Rally, [Oct] 1952 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Rally for Raises, Apr 8, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Teamsters Hospital Workers (Local 237) Demonstration, [1954] (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Budget/40-Hour Week Rally, Apr 11, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Bellevue Hospital Chapter Officers Installation/Local 420 Meeting, [Oct 16, 1955] (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Cafeteria Workers Strike (Local 933), [1955] (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Department of Parks Election, Jan 1956 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - AFSCME & Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee (GCEOC) Second Annual Conference, [Jul 28-29], 1956 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Meal Rights Rally (Local 420), [Aug 30, 1956] (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - DC 37 Organizing Drive, [Sep 17, 1956] (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Rally, [1956?] (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - American Labor Education Service Conference, [Feb 1957] (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Prayer Pilgrimage for Freedom (Local 420) Washington DC, [May 17, 1957] (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Mass Meeting for Collective Bargaining at St. Nicholas Arena, [Mar 27, 1958] (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Local 924 Demonstration, [May 28, 1957] (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Local 420 Organizing Drive (with Arthur Ochwada of Kenya Federation of Labor), [May 1958] (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Coney Island Aquarium Strike, [Jun 1958] (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art Strike (Local 1503), [Jun 1958] (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Zoo Strike (Local 1501), [Jun 1958] (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Democratic Party Candidates Rally, [Oct 1958] (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Youth House Strike (Local 1457), Oct 1958 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Youth March for Integrated Schools--Washington, DC, [Oct 1958] (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - New York State AFL-CIO First Constitutional Convention, [Dec 1958] (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Federation of the Handicapped Strike (Local 1707), [Feb 1959] (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Presbyterian Hospital Strike, [Mar 1959] (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - "Bermuda Day" Rally, [Mar 31, 1959] (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Garden Strike, [Apr 1959] (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Community Services Institute, [Jun 1959] (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Brooklyn Hospital Strike (Local 302), [Jun-Jul 1959] (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - AFL-CIO Convention, [Sep 1959] (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - DC 37 Fall Conference, [Aug, Oct 1959] (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Department of Welfare Rally (Local 371), [Oct 28, 1959] (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - ABC-TV Shoots: "The Hospital Story" (Local 420), "Crisis in the City", [Nov 1959] (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Various Gatherings: Unidentified, 1954-1959 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Triborough Bridge & Tunnel Agreement, [Feb 11, 1960] (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - 12th International Convention AFSCME, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Apr 1960 (Oversize Box XOS001, Folder 1)
    - Public Health Assistants Elections, [Mar 1960] (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Cultural Institutes Trip to Albany, [Feb 1960] (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Local 1655 Organizing at Board of Education, [Feb or Mar 1960] (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Medical Social Workers [at City Hall] (Local 420), [Jun 21, 1960] (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Labor Day Parade, [Sep 1960] (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - AFL-CIO Civil Rights Conference, [Sep 1960] (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Zoo Strike (Local 1501), [Apr 1961] (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Dr. Theodore H. Lang Testimonial Dinner (Local 832), May 4, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Demonstration in Support of Fordham Hospital (Local 420), [May 1961] (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - DC 37 Fall Conference, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Levitt Mayoral Campaign (United Labor Committee), [1961] (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - Beth-El Hospital Strike, Jun 1962 (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - Rally in Support of Private Non-profit Hospital Workers (Local 420 and others), [Jul 22, 1962] (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - Rally in Support of Private Industry New York City Workers, [Aug 7, 1962] (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Voter Registration Drive, [1962] (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - DC 37 Fall Conference, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Motor Vehicle Operators (MVO) Demonstration, Nov 1962 (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - AFSCME Convention, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Bellevue Hospital Demonstration (Local 420), [1962] (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - Demonstration in Support of Striking Newspaper Printers, [Jan 1963] (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - School Aides Gathering, Feb 1963 (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - DC 37 Spring Leadership Conference (with James Farmer), Apr 6, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - Demonstration in Support of Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers, [Apr 8, 1963] (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - Anti-Segregation Rally--New York (Oversize), [Apr 20, 1963] (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Stewards & Leadership Training Graduation, May 23, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 71)
    - Committee on Union Responsibility (COUR) Conference--Chicago, May 25, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 72)
    - White Castle Demonstrations--Brooklyn, Jul 1963 (Box 32, Folder 73)
    - March on Washington, Aug 28, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 74)
    - DC 37 Fall Conference, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 75)
    - New York State AFL-CIO Convention, Oct 1963 (Box 32, Folder 76)
    - New York City Board of Estimate Hearings/Salary Appeals, [1957-1963] (Box 32, Folder 77)
    - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE) School Bonds Demonstration, [1963?] (Box 32, Folder 78)
    - DC 30 Convention, [Jun 1964] (Box 32, Folder 79)
    - DC 37 Fall Conference, [Nov 1964] (Box 32, Folder 80)
    - Demonstration for Raises (to Salary Appeals Board), Dec 22, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 81)
    - Civil Rights March, Montgomery, AL--DC 37 Delegation, [Mar 1965] (Box 32, Folder 82)
    - Hospital Clerical Workers Drive, [May 1965] (Box 32, Folder 83)
    - James Farmer Visit (Local 420), Sep 15, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 84)
    - DC 37 Fall Conference, Nov 1965 (Box 32, Folder 85)
    - Locals 420/1784 Hospital Election, Dec 1965 (Box 32, Folder 86)
    - Bloomingdale's Strike, District 65 (DC 37 Support), 1965 (Box 32, Folder 87)
    - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE) Protest Against Schenley Industries, [1965 or Jan 1966] (Box 32, Folder 88)
    - Demonstration Against Open Competitive Exams for Senior Clerks, [Apr 13, 1966] (Box 32, Folder 89)
    - Marine Engineers Beneficial Association (MEBA) Demonstration, Apr 15, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 90)
    - James Farmer Tribute, Apr 16, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 91)
    - St. John's University Strike, Apr 18, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 92)
    - Various Gatherings: Unidentified, 1962-1966 (Box 32, Folder 93)
    - Demonstration Against Anthony Travia, [May 18, 1967] (Box 32, Folder 94)
    - City Employees Rally--Madison Square Garden, May 23, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 95)
    - Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB) Creation, [1967] (Box 32, Folder 96)
    - Demonstration by Social Service Clerical Workers Against Understaffing (Local 1549), [Feb 5, 1968] (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis, [Apr 1968] (Box 33, Folder 2)